most of you are doing bulgarian split
squats off a bench like this you either
go laces forward or
laces down
and this doesn't work that well in my
opinion because of this it's
uncomfortable for a lot of people for
this reason we use a single leg squat
stand to do bulgarian split squats
because this contours to the foot and
ankle complex now what if you don't have
a single leg squat stand i'm going to
show you three hacks now you can use a
barbell in a power rack like this but
you need to band it
so that the bar doesn't roll back and
forth
this way it doesn't move so victoria
places her back foot over the rounded
pad voila the bar doesn't move around
because the band keeps it in place a
better option is to use a smith machine
because it's stationary this doesn't
move just put the pad over the bar now
you can also do them off of a leg
extension or a leg curl machine just
like this
you'll find this much more comfortable
so give the rounded pad a try we think
you're gonna like it more